

Brooklyn, NY 11222 (123) 456-7890 stephen@beamjobs.com github.com/stephengreet

AWS certified solutions architect (CSA) with 4+ years experience building, deploying, and scaling robust AWS infrastructures for quickly growing web applications. I have a relentless focus on scalability, automation, and performance.

# **Experience**

## **Arcesium** - AWS DevOps Engineer

April 2019 - Present Pittsburgh, PA

- Designed, developed, managed, and ensured the reliability of a wide range of critical infrastructure systems, services, tools, and automation that provided the foundation for SaaS platform with a reach of 3.5 million users annually
- Developed next-generation strategic architecture and existing infrastructure management tools for AWS reducing costs by \$372,000 annually
- Troubleshooted critical production issues that the DevOps teams escalated resulting in a quick resolution of errors
- Worked closely with the application team to optimize integration between the SaaS software and infrastructure

#### **CentralReach** - DevOps Engineer

April 2016 - March 2019 Pittsburgh, PA

- Using Python, automated the deployment of 100+ cloud servers using Docker, Kubernetes and AWS
- Improved the existing infrastructure by automating the deployment of improvements resulting in yearly savings of \$161,000
- Fostered a culture of continuous integration & continuous delivery which reduced deployment time from 4 hours to 1 minute
- Implemented automated alerting around infrastructure issues which resulted in quicker and more efficient fixes leading to an improvement in the response time to critical errors by 85%
- Implemented automated reporting regarding the performance of the web app which saved over 10 hours of manual reporting time each week

# Education

### **University of Pittsburgh** - B.S. in Computer Science

September 2012 - April 2016

Pittsburgh, PA

## Skills

- CERTIFICATIONS
  - AWS Certified Solutions Architect (CSA)
- Docker/ Kubernetes
- AWS (CLI, EC2, S3, RDS)
- CI/CD Jenkins, Chef, Puppet, Git
- Python